(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-16T02:41:16.091472",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
MAKE IT, BREAK IT - FLOW GLOW 3D LIVE
You'll see!
Make it or break it
Make it? Break it?
Lock on
目と目が合えば I know
When our eyes meet, I know
キミこそが相棒
You're the partner for me
メロつかせる才能 (What?)
A talent for making people fall in love (What?)
Make it? Break it? Make it? Break it?
パッと見 天使でも (でも)
Though looking like an angel at first glance (At first)
中には潜むデーモン (デーモン)
There's a demon lurking inside (A demon)
So ギャップと愛嬌あれば最強
So with contrast and charm, we're invincible
Haterはシカト
Ignoring all the haters
「へー、あっそう！」
"Oh, is that so?"
一蓮托生オーガナイズ
Sharing the same fate, organized
退屈に用は無い
We have no time for boredom
一線画すよボーダーライン
Drawing a line at the border
届かない？しょーがない
Can't reach? Nothing you can do
ウチらが集えば バリ baddest (baddest)
When we get together, we're the absolute baddest (Baddest)
見惚れちゃうでしょ？
You can't take your eyes off us, right?
Look at me, look at me now...
置いてかない絶対
Never leaving you behind
ついて来て 5 MC's
Follow along, 5 MCs
本気のフライデーナイト
Friday night for real
Make it? Break it?
Make a revolution
アタシを貫け 傾け
Stay true to myself, stand out
夢に強引 Going, going on!
Pushing forcefully toward dreams, going, going on!
Break through and never stop
真ん中 ぶち抜け 行け
Blast right through the middle, go!
Can't get enough
You'll see!
Make it or break it
Make it? Break it?
Bang! Bang! Bang!
You'll see!
Make it or break it
Make it? Break it?
ほら、どっちにするの？
Come on, which one will you choose?
有象無象 沸かす FLOW GLOW
FLOW GLOW hype up the crowd
Ay 口先より行動
Ay, actions speak louder than words
If you wanna be マイメン
If you wanna be my main
よそ見とかナシで
No looking away
Warning! 没頭 ほら 没頭 ほら
Warning! Get immersed, come on, get immersed
味わっちゃって
Savor it all
Burning! もっと hotter もっと hotter
Burning! Getting hotter, getting hotter
ハイになっちゃって
Getting high on the vibe
置いてかない絶対
Never leaving you behind
ついて来て 5 MC's
Follow along, 5 MCs
本気のフライデーナイト
Friday night for real
Make it? Break it?
Brand new generation
感じるまま アガれ アガれ
Turn up, turn up, just as you feel
華麗に降臨 Only, only one
Gorgeously descending, the only, only one
退屈な Neverland
A boring Neverland
速攻で抜け出せ I say
Break out immediately, I say
Ready or not?
You'll see!
Make it or break it
Make it? Break it?
Bang! Bang! Bang!
You'll see!
Make it or break it
Make it? Break it?
朝まで Make some noise
Make some noise till morning
Make a revolution
アタシを貫け 傾け
Stay true to myself, stand out
夢に強引 Going, going on!
Pushing forcefully toward dreams, going, going on!
Break through and never stop
真ん中 ぶち抜け 行け
Blast right through the middle, go!
Can't get enough
You'll see!
Make it or break it
Make it? Break it?
Bang! Bang! Bang!
You'll see!
Make it or break it
Make it? Break it?
ほら、どっちにするの？
Come on, which one will you choose?
Yeah! This is FLOW GLOW from hololive DEV_IS!
お待たせしました！
Sorry to keep you waiting!
FLOW GLOW 3Dお披露目ライブ Make it! Break it!
FLOW GLOW 3D Debut Live: Make it! Break it!
楽しむ準備できてますかー！
Are you ready to have fun?!
搭載V8エンジン
Equipped with a V8 engine,
第7感持ってる原人
primitive humans with a 7th sense,
ロックするこの世界と全人類
locking onto this world and all humankind,
この5人でお前らをチェンジ
the 5 of us are gonna change you!
唸る4輪発射せよ
Launch with roaring 4-wheel drive!
皆さんサンキューサランヘヨ
Thank you everyone, saranghaeyo!
操る2台のturntable
Controlling two turntables,
獲る1番ここground 0
taking #1 right here at ground zero!
リスク超えて挑戦
Overcoming risks and taking on challenges,
チャンスもセットだ当然
naturally, chances come set with it!
登りあげる頂点
Climbing all the way to the top,
座布団積んでく笑点
stacking up cushions like Shoten!
乗り込む FG ROADSTER
Climbing into the FG ROADSTER,
特殊部隊 集合能力者
special forces, unit of ability users,
この歴史に名を彫る彫刻家
sculptors carving our names into history,
ぶっちぎりでおきざり後続車
leaving trailing cars far behind in our dust!
今高速でぶち抜いていく大気圏
Now blasting through the atmosphere at high speed!
エンジンからジェットの炎 揺れている怪気炎
Jet flames swaying from the engine, roaring hot,
眼下に広がる大地を超えていく回帰線
surpassing the line of tropics beyond the vast land below,
バックミラーにBig Blueが映っている IBM
the Big Blue reflected in the rearview mirror, IBM!
打ち上げ台から飛んでくうちら世代
Our generation flying off from the launchpad,
この燃料朽ち果てない
this fuel will never burn out,
銀河で寿司食べたい
we wanna eat sushi in the galaxy!
見えてるでかいビジョン
Seeing a grand vision,
燃えてるメンバー一同
all members burning with passion,
ただいま現在進行形 超えてく世界規模
presently ongoing, surpassing world scale!
叶うはずだ Won't stop
It will come true, won't stop,
心臓がモンスター
a heart like a monster,
Aliens turn it up
FG party hard
光る Tesla Roadster
Shining Tesla Roadster,
Heavy booster
目覚めていく本能
instincts awakening,
青い炎
blue flames!
BFF let's go out, so get in the car
0から宇宙まで囚われず
unbound from zero all the way to space!
走る FG ROADSTER
Running FG ROADSTER,
唸る booster
roaring booster,
FLOW GLOW the space to be
イチャ chase me
Icha chase me!
フロミの皆さん、楽しんでますかー！
Everyone in FLOWME, are you having fun?!
FGちゃんたちも、もっともっとかます準備できてるー？
Are you FG girls ready to kick it up even more?!
FG ROADSTERに続いては、この曲！「24K GOLD」！
Following FG ROADSTER, here's this song! "24K GOLD"!
我々は翔る super girl
We are flying super girls,
金ピカの光 異次元
glittering light from another dimension,
荒れ果てた世界 パトロール
patrolling a desolate world,
解き放て 踊れ
unleash and dance!
私達 存在が純金
Our very existence is pure gold,
いつでも 万端な準備
always fully prepared,
まるで 無敵の宇宙人
just like invincible aliens!
春麗よりも俊敏
Nimbler than Chun-Li,
サイドブレーキない突撃
an assault with no handbrake,
ハイボルテージ 毎回素敵
high voltage, wonderful every time,
催促です 愛をくれ
demanding it: give us love!
今乗っかってある波の上
Riding high on this wave right now!
変人 凡人 才人も
Weirdos, ordinary folks, geniuses too,
みんなで遊ぼう 最近どう？
let's all play together, how've you been lately?
流れてる flow like 合気道
Flowing along like Aikido,
戦闘力 マイティ・ソー
combat power like Mighty Thor!
純度100%
100% purity,
この爆発力 マクラーレン
this explosive power like McLaren,
メッキに興味ない ルパン三世
no interest in plating, Lupin III,
この輝きなら ツタンカーメン
with this shine, Tutankhamun!
髪 風受け なびかせ
Letting our hair flutter in the wind,
good, good, groove your body
let it rock, rock, rock, rock, rock, rock on
心を突き動かせ
Stir up your heart,
good, good, groove your body
level up, up, up, up, up, up
look at me now
身に纏う flight suitは
The flight suit we wear,
24k gold
is 24K GOLD,
ready to go
深い闇照らす輝き
A radiance illuminating deep darkness,
24k gold
上にゆこう
let's go up!
空飛んでいる what's up
Flying through the sky, what's up?
このケープが翼
This cape is our wings,
滾っている power
boiling power,
戦ってる super girl
fighting super girls!
全身駆け巡る満タンのガソリン
Full tank of gasoline coursing through our bodies,
黄金の流星だ パッと見
a golden meteor at first glance,
忍者みたい 服部半蔵
like a ninja, Hanzo Hattori,
強くて可愛くってかっこいい
strong, cute, and cool!
戦う 高鳴る
Fighting, throbbing,
黄金の戦士 現る
the Golden Warriors appear!
渋谷 新宿 原宿
Shibuya, Shinjuku, Harajuku,
風となり ちはやぶる
becoming the wind, fierce and swift!
絶対 撤退 命令ない
There's absolute, no retreat order,
アベンジャーズみたいな精鋭隊
an elite squad like the Avengers!
生成AIにはないオーラ
An aura that generative AI doesn't have,
纏ってる 輝く生命体
clad as glowing living entities!
身任せ
Surrendering yourself,
受けナビゲーション
follow the navigation,
Go Go Go 評判
Go Go Go reputation,
Ready Go Go Go Go Go
心を突き動かせ
Stir your heart,
Go Go Go 評判
Go Go Go reputation,
Ready Level Up Pa Pa Pa Pa Pa Pa Pa
身に纏うフライスーツ
put on a mini flight suit,
宛先に OK, Go! Ready to go!
Destination OK, Go! Ready to go!
深い闇照らす 輝き
The light illuminating the deep darkness,
解き放て
unleash it!
新次元のステージ FG FIRE!
A new dimension's stage, FG FIRE!
FG!
Jump Jump Jump Jump Jump Jump FG!
Run Go Run Go Run Go
FLOW GLOW 3Dライブお披露目を
Everyone watching FLOW GLOW's 3D Live reveal,
ご覧の皆さん！
welcome!
What's up!
キター！ FLOW GLOW です！
We're here! We are FLOW GLOW!
先ほどは「FG ROADSTER」と「24K GOLD」をメドレー形式でお届けしました！
Just now, we performed a medley of "FG ROADSTER" and "24K GOLD"!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
いや、最初からド派手な登場すぎませんか？
Man, wasn't that intro super flashy?
どうやったらみんなを驚かせられるか考えた結果だよね
It's the result of thinking how we could surprise everyone!
一番ド派手なもんでいこうって言って、モニターを突き破ってきました！
We decided to go with the flashiest thing and broke through the monitor!
見たことないよね！
We've never seen anything like that before!
そんなハチャメチャすぎる私たちなんですけど、まずは自己紹介の方からさせていただけたらなと思います！
While we might be totally chaotic, we'd like to start with our self-introductions!
それでは私から！
Starting with me!
私の音に酔いな！ In the house!
Get drunk on my sound! In the house!
FLOW GLOWのリーダー、響咲リオナです！ Bra-bra!
I'm the leader of FLOW GLOW, Isaki Riona! Bra-bra!
次はニコ！
Next up is Niko!
ニコたんが来たー！ hololive DEV_IS FLOW GLOWのお笑い担当、輪堂ニコですね！
Niko-tan is here! From hololive DEV_IS FLOW GLOW, I'm the comedy rep, Rindo Niko!
ニコたん大漁！
Niko-tan big catch!
すぅちゃん！
Suu-chan!
すぅちゃんにくるのね！
Passing it to Suu-chan!
じぴじぴわーす！ Suuの充電足りてる？ hololive DEV_IS FLOW GLOWのイラスト担当、水宮すぅでーす！
Jipi-jipi wahs! Is your Suu battery charged? From hololive DEV_IS FLOW GLOW, the illustration rep, Mizumiya Suu!
次はちーちゃん！
Next is Chii-chan!
はい！ エンジン全開 Let's Go! FLOW GLOWのDJ兼運転手担当、神成シハルでーす！ 今日も盛り上がっていこうね！
Yes! Engine full throttle, Let's Go! FLOW GLOW's DJ and driver, Kaminari Chihan! Let's get hyped today!
次はヴィヴィ！
Next is Vivi!
はい！ 行きますよ！ せーの、うー！
Yes! Here we go! Ready, set, ooh!
ヴィヴィ！ いつもキラキラな？ きらきらヴィヴィです！ わー！ みんな今日も盛り上がっていきましょう！ よろしく！
Vivi! Always sparkling? Sparkling Vivi! Whoa! Let's all turn up today! Nice to meet you!
よろしくお願いします！
We look forward to having fun with you!
今日は私たち5人で最高のライブをお届けしていくぞー！
Today, the five of us are going to deliver the ultimate live show!
行くぞー！
Let me hear you!
さて、すでにお気づきかと思いますが、ついにFLOW GLOWも3Dデビューしましたー！
Now, as you might have already noticed, FLOW GLOW has finally made our 3D debut!
めでたい！ 嬉しいねー！
Congratulations! We're so happy!
ちなみにヴィヴィ、3Dになった自分の体を見てどう思いますか？
By the way, Vivi, what do you think looking at your body now that it's in 3D?
いやー、こんなにキューティー、セクシー、ヘルシーでね！ みんなもっとヴィヴィのこと好きになっちゃったなー！ ほんまやで！
Well, I'm just so cutie, sexy, and healthy! Everyone must have fallen even more in love with Vivi! For real!
なんだこのポーズまじで！
What is with that pose, seriously?!
放送事故になるから！ BANされる！
That's gonna cause a broadcast accident! We'll get banned!
はーい、ありがとね！ ちーんはどう？
Okay, thank you! How about Chihan?
はい！ ちーはんはもちろん、この太ももをご覧ください！
Yes! For Chihan, of course, please look at these thighs!
見て！ 見て！ もっとくれ！
Look! Look! Give us more!
太ももアピールタイプだからね！
Because she's the thigh appeal type!
すぅちゃんはどうですか？
How about Suu-chan?
はい！ すぅはまあ、かっこいいかな、みたいな。やっぱイケてるかな、みたいな。
Yes! Suu is, well, kinda cool... totally awesome, like...
いやいや、そんなキャラじゃなかったよ！
Hey now, that wasn't your character at all!
バレちゃったな！
You got caught!
え、ニコたん？
Wait, Niko-tan?
ニコたん完全に虎！
Niko-tan is completely a tiger!
ライブで踊るんだから、それ四足になれないでしょ！
Since we're dancing at a live performance, I can't stay on all fours!
見たことないよ！
Never seen anything like it!
で、リオナはどうですか？
And how about you, Riona?
そうですね、まあ、私もちょっぴりセクシー？
Well, I suppose... I'm a little bit sexy too?
セクシーダンスをこの体でお披露目できるかなと思うと、すごく嬉しいです！
Thinking that I can show off a sexy dance with this body makes me super happy!
素晴らしい！ 可愛い！ 楽しみだね！
Wonderful! Cute! Looking forward to it!
そんな私たち5人でお届けする3Dライブ、そのハッシュタグについてニコ、説明よろしくお願いします！
For the 3D live brought to you by the 5 of us, Niko, please explain the hashtag!
はーい！ 今日の3Dライブのハッシュタグ、右上をご覧ください！
Yesss! For today's 3D live hashtag, please look at the top right!
ハッシュタグ FG3Dライブ です！
The hashtag is #FG3Dライブ!
スクショにこのハッシュタグを加えて、Xでたくさんポストしてください！
Add this hashtag to your screenshots and post a lot on X!
お願いします！ トレンド1位目指すぞ！
Please do! Let's aim for #1 on trending!
配信を見てくれてるみんなね、ぜひコメントでこのFGちゃんたちに声援を送ってください！ よろしくお願いします！
Everyone watching the stream, please send your cheers to the FG girls in the comments! Thank you!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
はい、そしてライブの後半にはサプライズや重大発表もありますので、ぜひ最後まで楽しんでいただけたら嬉しいです！
Yes! And in the second half of the live, we have surprises and major announcements, so we'd be really happy if you enjoy until the very end!
お願いしまーす！まばたきしないでね！
Please do! Don't even blink!
てかさ、千早さん？ フータロー置いてるのまずいかも...
By the way, Chihaya-san? Leaving Fuutaro parked there might be bad...
え、ダメなの？かっこいいよ？ 東京あの路上駐車ダメ...切られちゃうよ！
Eh, is it bad? It's cool! Street parking isn't allowed in Tokyo... It'll get ticketed!
だから、まあ繋いでどこかから止めてきてもらって... 止めてきてー！
So, while we stall, have someone go park it somewhere... Please go park it!
いってきます！ じゃあ次の曲行こうか...
I'm off! Well then, shall we go to the next song...
冗談はさておき、1曲目から『FG ROADSTER』と『24K GOLD』をメドレー形式でお送りしてきました！
Jokes aside, right from the first song, we brought you a medley of "FG ROADSTER" and "24K GOLD"!
なんと！その『FG ROADSTER』のサビの振り付けは、すーちゃんがしてくれたんだよね！
And amazingly, the choreography for the chorus of "FG ROADSTER" was done by Su-chan!
やっぱね、ちょっとかっこいい感じで... あ、千早！法定速度守れよ！
Yeah, with a cool vibe... Ah, Chihaya! Obey the speed limit!
かっこいい感じでこっからの振りを作らせていただいたんですけど... 皆さんもぜひいつか踊ってください！
I made the choreography from here with a cool style... Everyone, please try dancing it too someday!
ヴィヴィたんはメドレーやってみてどうだった？
Vivitan, how was doing the medley for you?
やっぱりずっとみんなに初めて披露した時から... リリースした時から歌とダンス一緒に見てもらいたいなと思ってたから、こうやって見てもらうことができてめっちゃ嬉しいです！
Ever since we first performed it... actually, since we released it, I've always wanted everyone to see the song and dance together, so I'm super happy everyone finally gets to see it!
かっこよかったー？ かっこよかったよー！ にこはどうだった？
Was it cool? It was so cool! Nico, how about you?
にこも楽しかった！いろんな曲をくっつけて踊るとか... ごめん、今頭真っ白で何喋ってるか全然分からないや！
Nico had fun too! Connecting various songs to dance... Sorry, my mind is completely blank right now and I have no idea what I'm talking about!
そうだね、でもやっぱりデビュー通して... ちょっと待って！みんな緊張してる！
That's right, but through our debut... Wait a minute! Everyone is so nervous!
深呼吸！深呼吸！
Deep breath! Deep breath!
どうしたどうした？何してる？ 前の車ですか？開けてくれー！
What's wrong? What are you doing? Is that the car in front? Open up!
4人の曲の感想を聞きたかったんだけど、私達緊張してボロボロ言ってる...
I wanted to hear the four of their thoughts on the songs, but we were so nervous we were rambling gibberish...
デビューしてから2曲出したオリジナル曲をこうやって皆さんの前で動きありで披露できて本当に素敵でしたし、これからもFLOW GLOWのことをよろしくお願いします！
Being able to perform our two original songs released since debut in front of everyone with full movement was really wonderful, so please keep supporting FLOW GLOW!
ありがとう！止めてきてくれたのもありがとうね！
Thank you! And thank you for going to park it!
そうだよ、ちょっとファンの人の車が多すぎて駐車場全然空いてなくて...
Yeah, there were so many fans' cars that there were no open parking spots at all...
帰り気をつけてよ！危ないからね！
Be careful on the way back! It's dangerous!
じゃあそろそろみんなもライブ見たいのかなと思うので、次の曲に参りたいと思います！
Alright, I think everyone wants to see the live performance soon, so let's move on to the next song!
ついでにモニターも何か新しいものになりました！
By the way, the monitor has also changed to something new!
まだまだライブは続くので、ますます盛り上がっていきましょう！
The live performance is still going, so let's get even more hyped!
それでは聴いてください、『LOAD』。
Please listen to: "LOAD".
読み込みが完了しました
Loading complete.
1, 2, 3, Jump!
世界中に配信するライブ ここはホロ
Live streaming to the whole world, this is Holo
80億の星の lights 照らす心
Lights of 8 billion stars illuminating the heart
通知が鳴る
A notification rings
It's time to show my digital world
寝かせない朝まで
Won't let you sleep until morning
カーソル合わせる絵文字の上
Moving the cursor over the emojis
スタジオにいる今日も 歌詞を書いているノートに
In the studio today as well, writing lyrics in my notebook
変わる景色、相当 気づけばいたよ東京
Scenery changing quite a bit, before I knew it I was in Tokyo
夜空をみる首都高 乗る月に向かうボート
Capital Expressway viewing the night sky, riding a boat bound for the moon
みんなに見せる証拠 力になれることを
Proof to show everyone that I can be a source of strength
ネガなマインド捨て 見てるだけじゃ意味ない
Ditching negative minds, just watching means nothing
夢じゃなくなった夢 負けず嫌いで有名
A dream that's no longer just a dream, famous for hating to lose
どこにもない終点 君と見た星空の下
An endpoint that's nowhere to be found, under the starry sky I saw with you
届きそうな手
Hands feeling so close to reaching
このデバイスがあればどこへでも
With this device, wherever I go
行ける気がするよ 続く one way
I feel like I can get there, the one way continues
Stay with me by my side 遠いとこへ 2人で
Stay with me by my side, to a far-off place, the two of us
この地球から virtual world
From this Earth to the virtual world
気にしない今何時 何万キロ離れても
Not caring what time it is, no matter how many tens of thousands of kilometers away
My team FLOW GLOW すぐ行動開始
My team FLOW GLOW, starting action right away
チャット止まらない 24 調子がいい今日
Chat doesn't stop 24/7, feeling good today
カメラにするはいチーズ
Say cheese to the camera
乗っ取ってる電波塔から 放送する世界に配信
Broadcasting from the hijacked transmission tower, streaming to the world
みてみなこのスタイル Yeah 負ける気すらナイ
Take a look at this style, yeah, don't even feel like losing
捨てていく無駄な pride できるよこのくらい
Throwing away useless pride, I can do at least this much
みんなで今夜も party all night
Party all night with everyone again tonight
日々日々に上がる price やれるなら u better try
Price going up day by day, if you can, u better try
世界中に配信するライブ ここはホロ
Live streaming to the whole world, this is Holo
80億の星の lights 照らす心
Lights of 8 billion stars illuminating the heart
変わる景色 奏
Changing scenery, sounding out
気づけばいたよ東京
Before I knew it, I was in Tokyo
夜空を見上げるスターコー
Looking up at the night sky, star call
昇る月に向かうポート
A port facing the rising moon
みんなに見せるよ証拠
I'll show everyone the proof
力になれる言葉
Words that can give strength
一生に一度しかない初登校
First day of school, once in a lifetime
吐き出す風全部味方にしたい
I want to turn all the blowing winds onto my side
好きなように生きていける世界で
In a world where I can live as I like
広げていけるこの視界
Expanding this view of mine
爆音鳴らして行こう
Let's blast the loud music and go
音が狂うライヴ
A live show where the sound goes crazy
震わすこの針
Trembling this needle
踊れレッツパーティガール
Dance, let's party girl
世界中に配信するライブ ここは本堂
A live broadcast worldwide, this is the main stage
80億の星のライト照らすここから
Lit up by 8 billion star lights from right here
筋がないタイプでしょう なでしこ
An unpredictable type, right? Nadeshiko
音に任せるの朝まで
Leaving it to the sound until morning
高鳴る夜今日も 歌詞を書いているノートに
On this thrilling night, writing lyrics in my notebook again today
変わる景色 奏
Changing scenery, sounding out
気づけばいたよ東京
Before I knew it, I was in Tokyo
夜空を見上げるスターコー
Looking up at the night sky, star call
昇る月に向かうポート
A port facing the rising moon
みんなに見せるよ証拠
I'll show everyone the proof
力になれる言葉
Words that can give strength
パジャマのままジョインする morning meeting
I join the morning meeting in my pajamas
頭空っぽになる my ルーティン
My routine leaves my head empty
始まりから終わりまで mute screen
Mute screen from start to finish
朝起きてえらい
Great for waking up in the morning
傘持ってってえらい
Great for bringing an umbrella
ネガティブあり得ない
Negatives are impossible
自由にかえりらい
Rewrite your mood freely
背伸びしない 遠慮しない
Don't stretch yourself, don't hold back
やばいくらいゆるい my vibe
My vibe is crazy carefree
描いてくカラーは自分次第
The colors I draw are up to me
オチない話を続ける鬼才
A genius who keeps telling stories without punchlines
行き先決めないっていうフリースタイル
A freestyle of not deciding where to go next
指さされたけど気分はフライ
Pointed fingers at me, but my mood is fly
眠たい 眠たい 眠らない tonight
Sleepy, sleepy, not sleeping tonight
無敵の状態
State of invincibility
態度デカいのは長所に書いていいってお母さんが言ってた
Mom said having a big attitude is okay to put down as a strength
フィルター越しの snap でピース
Peace sign with a snap through a filter
本当の事は虹の彼方に
The truth is beyond the rainbow
リアルもフェイクも just like a piece
Both real and fake, just like a piece
So who decides what's real?
Not cool, but good, good enough
I'm still good, good, good enough
ちょっと loose, but good, good enough
A bit loose, but good, good enough
I'm still good, good, good enough
もっと fuel, but good, good enough
More fuel, but good, good enough
I'm still good, good, good enough
Not good, but good, good enough
誤字 脱字 日常茶飯事
Typos and omissions are everyday occurrences
また見過ごし 寝過ごし それも生きてる証
Overlooking and oversleeping again, that's proof I'm alive
未完成だからこそつくプレ値
Being unfinished is why it gets a premium value
Good, good enough
磨けば必ず光る前提
Under the assumption that it will shine if polished
Good, good enough
夢見てた頃の自分はチャイルド
Back when I was dreaming, I was just a child
今日まで集めたフル装備でファイト
Fighting with full gear collected up until today
ビビりだからこそ高めるマインド
Raising my mindset precisely because I'm a coward
褒めたい 褒めたい たまに褒められたい
Want to praise, want to praise, want to be praised sometimes
言葉じゃ足りない
Words aren't enough
愛想がいいのは赤ちゃんの時からっておばあちゃんも言ってた
Grandma also said I've been friendly since I was a baby
パジャマのままジョインする morning meeting
I join the morning meeting in my pajamas
頭空っぽになる my ルーティン
My routine leaves my head empty
始まりから終わりまで mute screen
Mute screen from start to finish
So who's in trouble, anyway?
Not cool, but good, good enough
I'm still good, good, good enough
ちょっと loose, but good, good enough
A bit loose, but good, good enough
I'm still good, good, good enough
もっと fuel, but good, good enough
More fuel, but good, good enough
I'm still good, good, good enough
Not good, but good, good enough
フィルター越しの snap でピース
Peace sign with a snap through a filter
本当の事は虹の彼方に
The truth is beyond the rainbow
リアルもフェイクも just like a piece
Both real and fake, just like a piece
So who decides what's real?
パジャマのままジョインする morning meeting
I join the morning meeting in my pajamas
頭空っぽになる my ルーティン
My routine leaves my head empty
始まりから終わりまで mute screen
Mute screen from start to finish
SOLO PERFORMANCE
[Title: SOLO PERFORMANCE]
Once upon a time
There was a little girl
君によく似た
She really looked like you
Oh darling 君に似てた
Oh darling, she was just like you
彼女はまるでタイガーアイ
She was just like a tiger's eye
無数の欲より大事な
A dream more precious than any kind of greed...
夢を見つけては 掴んでしまった
...she found it and made it hers.
ある夜 雨が降ってた
One night, it was raining
濡れた瞳にぼやけた
Dewy eyes saw a blurry light
嘘のように美しい
It was beautiful, like a lie
ダリアが微笑んでた
A dahlia was smiling at her
I want the same one
それが欲しいのと 吐き捨ててこう言った
"That's what I want," she spat out and said
引き換えに何が欲しい？
"What do you want in return?"
奏でろ 讃美歌
"Now go on and play that hymn"
無知なメロディーは ハイ
"A melody of ignorance is high"
たかが心なら差し上げたいわ
"If all you want is my heart, I'd love to give it away"
And then I... 甘ったるいお願いね
And then I... What a sickly sweet wish
そして彼女は Just a ダリアのように
And then she... Just like a dahlia
No... ダリア
No... Dahlia
Just a ダリアのように
Just like a dahlia
ダリア... ダリア
Dahlia... Dahlia
改めまして 響咲リオナです！名前 覚えて帰ってください！
Once again, I'm Riona Isaki! Please remember my name!
乱心 内心 邁進 ego
Distracted heart, inner self, pushing forward ego
Up & down Always get into trouble
楽しい 正しい 嬉しい でも
Fun, right, happy, but...
平常 me, sold out
Calm me, sold out
あれナシ これナシ
Without this, without that
合わせる段々 敵なし
Gradually matching, no enemies around
己の way?
My own way?
違える (No, no) またゼロへ Get away
Straying off (No, no), back to zero, get away
(Oh no, no, no...)
Whisper to my ears
Oh give me some more details
手招き脱して 勝ち
Escaping the beckoning hand, victory
No way slipping and breaking down
かませ 急上昇
Fire it up, rapid surge
放て 絶好調 Own way now
Unleash it, in peak condition, own way now
Better show what I gotta gotta show!
Ima shake it, let's go. Next!
変幻 理想像
Ever-changing ideal image
Come again, 熱狂
Come again, frenzy
Hey show me what you got
I'm breaking down pretty me
Next side Next side... 楽しんだれ Upboomboom!
Next side, next side... enjoy it, Upboomboom!
Trip in the dark...
Such a funny thing for me to explain
It's ok even if you don't understand
I just wanna make you roll
ルールはない Unchain
There are no rules, unchain
頭と心 Awake now
Mind and heart, awake now
アブラカタ blah blah blah 幻なら
Abracadabra blah blah blah, if it's an illusion...
無理 無理 無理
Impossible, impossible, impossible
価値なし無視 Ah, just do it!
Worthless, ignore it, ah, just do it!
Are you ready let's play game!
Are you ready? Let's play the game!
万人万事愛しては
Loving everyone and everything...
一蓮托生 三千世界
...sharing the same fate across the vast universe.
Dancing 突進 童心 Get up
Dancing, rushing in, childish heart, get up!
全方位 Call out
Call out in all directions
人生も来世も
Both in this life and the next life...
I wish days were longer than 24
曇りなくいたいの Yeah
I want to stay without a cloud of doubt, yeah
I'm feeling really mellow
Oh I wanna feel more
たまにはわがままに
Selfish once in a while
Now hey, come in and turn it loud
鳴らせ 鼓動を
Make your heartbeat resound
醒ませ 最高潮 Own way now
Awaken the climax, own way now
Better show what I gotta gotta show...
Gotta show what I wanna wanna show!
Ima shake it, let's go. Next!
変幻 理想像
Ever-changing ideal image
Come again, 熱狂
Come again, frenzy
Hey show me what you got
I'm breaking down pretty me
Next side Next side... 楽しんだれ Upboomboom!
Next side, next side... enjoy it, Upboomboom!
Na na na yeah
Na na na na na na na na
Let's make it loud!
La-ta-ta-tat!
Next side Next side...
楽しんだれ Upboomboom!
Enjoy it, Upboomboom!
Yeah yeah yeah
欲望に満ちた青年団
Young Men Full of Desire
一度はあの光を見たんだよ とっても綺麗で
Once, I saw that light, and it was so beautiful.
でも今思えば汚かった あれはいわゆる Bad Day Dreams
But looking back now, it was dirty—what you'd call Bad Day Dreams.
光が眩し過ぎて 周りが見えず ただただ日々を
The light was too dazzling to see around me, just wasting...
棒に振ってたあの日 今だから笑えるよ
...my days back then. I can laugh about it now.
一度はあの幕を開けたんだよ とっても重くて
Once, I opened that curtain, and it was so heavy.
プレッシャー イヤ味 それに勝つために ただ嫌なヤツで
Pressure and spite—to beat them, I was just a nasty guy.
そして気がつくと真っ暗な部屋に 一人ぼっちだった
And before I realized it, I was all alone in a pitch-black room.
終わった... もう戻れない... なんて... 歩くのもやめた...
"It's over... I can't go back..." I even stopped walking...
でも I'm not alone, I'm not alone, We're not, We're not, We're not alone
But I'm not alone, I'm not alone, We're not, We're not, We're not alone.
お金じゃ買えないもの手に入れて
Getting my hands on things money can't buy,
もう一度光浴びて そして今度は騙されぬように
basking in the light once more, and this time, so we won't be deceived,
僕らは今目指すよ 欲望に満ちた青年団
we now aim to be young men full of desire.
誰かが言った言葉 それすらその時は流して
The words someone said—I even brushed them off back then.
今になって気づいたよ 欲望に負けた少年団
Only now have I realized; young boys defeated by desire.
So I know you know, You know I know, We have, We have, We have to go
囚われないように 上を向いて歩く
Facing upward so as not to be trapped, I walk...
もう一度光浴びて そして今度は騙されぬように
Basking in the light once more, and this time, so we won't be deceived,
僕らは今目指すよ 欲望に満ちた青年団
we now aim to be young men full of desire.
誰かが言った言葉 それすらその時は流して
The words someone said—I even brushed them off back then.
今になって気づいたよ 欲望に負けた少年団
Only now have I realized; young boys defeated by desire.
ありがとうございました
Thank you very much!
かがみ
Mirror
朝起きて まず確認 今日もいい感じだね
Waking up in the morning, first checking—looking good today too!
1年365日 私のこと一番見てる人
365 days a year, the person who looks at me the most.
好きですと言えるのは 当たり前とかじゃない
Being able to say "I love you" isn't something to take for granted.
1日8万6400秒 ずっと付き合ってくんだから
86,400 seconds a day, because we're staying together forever!
ママから聞いたことあるわ
I've heard it from my mom before:
似た人を好きになるんじゃなくて
You don't fall for someone who resembles you,
好きな人には似るものらしいです 本当です
but rather, you come to resemble the one you love. It's true!
みんな思ったことあるわ
Everyone's thought about it before:
目を開けたら違う自分になって
"When I open my eyes, I'll turn into a different me."
いやいやもっと真剣に変身
No, no, transforming even more seriously...
マスカラの夜は フルフルル
Night of mascara, furururu...
あれ？可愛くなりすぎちゃったかな？
Oh? Did I become too cute?
もう さすがに盛りすぎちゃったかな？
Did I overdo my makeup a bit too much?
あなたの真似したんです
I was actually imitating you,
だって 超大好きなんだから
because I love you super much!
かがみよかがみ もうちょっとだけ
Mirror, mirror, just a little bit more,
可愛くなってもいいのかな？
is it okay if I become cute?
いつだって正直にいて
Always stay honest,
それで 秘密 秘密 秘密のいい子ちゃんにはなれない
and so I can't become a secret, secret good girl.
そんなこと全部お見通しです
I see right through all of that,
だって逆に 秘密 秘密 秘密は私達にはいらない
because on the contrary, secret, secret secrets are not needed between us.
だけどあなたが秘密にしたいほど
However, to the extent that you'd want to keep it a secret,
可愛くなりすぎちゃったかも
I might have become way too cute.
朝起きて「そうだ、休み！」
Waking up in the morning, "Right, it's a day off!"
やりたいことありすぎ
I have way too many things I want to do.
1日は24時間っていうけど ずっと起きてるわけでもない
They say a day has 24 hours, but it's not like I'm awake the whole time.
帰ったらまた確認「当たり前」とかじゃない
Checking again after getting home, it's not like it's taken for granted.
とにかく自分を大事にしましょう
Anyway, let's take good care of ourselves.
ずっと付き合っていくんだから
Since we're going to be living with ourselves forever.
ママから聞いたことあるわ
I've heard this from mom before:
10時から2時は寝るのがよくて
"It's best to sleep between 10 PM and 2 AM,
6時以降は食べないほうがいいって
and it's better not to eat after 6 PM."
いや無理です！
Yeah right, impossible!
みんな思ったことあるわ
Everyone has thought about this before:
寝てる間に変わらないのかな？
"Won't things change while I'm sleeping?"
いやいやいや マジで本気に変身した！
No, no, no, I seriously transformed for real!
マスカラの夜は フルフルル
Night of mascara, furururu...
あれ？可愛くなりすぎちゃっていい？
Oh? Is it okay if I become too cute?
本当に盛りすぎちゃっていい？
Is it really okay if I overdo my makeup?
あなたのこと好きです
I like you,
だって 超前向きなんだから
because I'm super forward-looking!
かがみよかがみ もうちょっとだけ
Mirror, mirror, just a little bit more,
可愛くなってもいいのかな？
is it okay if I become cute?
いつだって正直にいて
Always stay honest,
もう大好きです 大好きです
I already love you so much, love you so much,
だけど目の前の君にいっていいのかな？
but is it okay to tell you right in front of me?
自分に今 魔法かけます
I'll cast a spell on myself now,
嘘でもかかったふりしてね？
so pretend it worked, even if it's a lie, okay?
でも私もしあなたも 嘘がつけない
But neither I nor you can tell a lie,
そういうやつだからさ
because that's just the kind of people we are.
マスカラの夜は フルフルル
Night of mascara, furururu...
あれ？可愛くなりすぎちゃっていい？
Oh? Is it okay if I become too cute?
本当に盛りすぎちゃっていい？
Is it really okay if I overdo my makeup?
あなたのこと好きです
I like you,
だって 超前向きなんだから
because I'm super forward-looking!
かがみよかがみ もうちょっとだけ
Mirror, mirror, just a little bit more,
可愛くなってもいいのかな？
is it okay if I become cute?
いつだって正直にいて
Always stay honest.
あれ？可愛くなりすぎちゃったかな？
Oh? Did I become too cute?
もう さすがに盛りすぎちゃったかな？
Did I overdo my makeup a bit too much?
あなたの真似したんです
I was actually imitating you,
だって 超大好きなんだから
because I love you super much!
かがみよかがみ もうちょっとだけ
Mirror, mirror, just a little bit more,
可愛くなってもいいのかな？
is it okay if I become cute?
いつだって正直にいて
Always stay honest,
それで 秘密 秘密 秘密のいい子ちゃんにはなれない
and so I can't become a secret, secret good girl.
そんなこと全部お見通しです
I see right through all of that,
だって逆に 秘密 秘密 秘密は私達にはいらない
because on the contrary, secret, secret secrets are not needed between us.
だけどあなたが秘密にしたいほど
However, to the extent that you'd want to keep it a secret,
可愛くなりすぎちゃったかもね
I might have become way too cute, huh?
笑わない夜の途中
In the middle of a smiling-less night,
灯りを忘れた空には
in the sky that forgot its light,
戻れない日の指切りを
a pinky promise from an unreturnable day,
歌詞をピアノの代わりに
using lyrics instead of a piano,
鳥になった
became a bird.
だから物が落とす影を追っていたら
So, if I chase the shadows cast by things,
真っ暗に紛れて混ざって
getting lost and blended in the pitch black,
見つけられないままで
remaining unable to be found,
いくつめかのドアを開けて
opening several doors,
繰り返す景色を泳ぐ
swimming through repeating scenery.
心がまだ追いつけないまま
While my heart still can't catch up,
そのためだけに動いてる
I move solely for that purpose.
これはきっと 帰り道
This is surely the way back home,
夢の向こうに続く道
the path continuing beyond dreams.
ほころびた歌を纏えば
If I wear a tattered song,
何も怖くはない
there is nothing to fear.
命は理由に出会えた
My life met its reason,
燃えて消える意味を知った
learned the meaning of burning away.
その東 視界を照らした
Illuminating the vision in the east,
青く 青く どこまでも
blue, blue, endlessly,
明日が全てを失っても
even if tomorrow loses everything.
あなたのことだけは
If you want me to sing only of you,
歌ってほしい
if that's what you want,
ならば私は戦える
then I can keep fighting.
たとえこの耳が聞こえないとしても
Even if my ears can no longer hear.
思い果たせなくなった虹を覚えている空には
In the sky that remembers the unfulfilled rainbow,
くたびれた靴が響くよ
worn-out shoes echo.
それでも歩いていると
Even so, as I keep walking,
つかむ手すら解けた
even the hand I held slipped away.
言葉を忘れない手のひら
Palms that won't forget those words,
指を二つにして隠して
crossing my fingers to hide them,
強さに変える魔法を
the magic that turns them into strength.
あとどれだけ息をしたら
How many more breaths must I take
これでよかったと思える
before I can feel that this was right?
心はずっと欠片だから
Because my heart has always been in fragments,
欠片の全部で動いている
it moves with every single piece.
これはきっと帰り道
This must be the way back home.
あの人と同じじゃなくていい
It doesn't have to be the same as theirs,
ただもう一度だけ会いたい
I just want to meet once more.
何も怖くはない
Nothing frightens me anymore.
泣かないでって祈るのは
Praying "Please don't cry"
足跡の下の涙
are the tears beneath our footsteps.
迷いをのけたつま先で
With toes that cast aside hesitation,
進め 進め 魂ごと
advance, advance with your whole soul.
正確かどうかなんてことよりも
Rather than whether it's correct or not,
あなたのいる世界が笑ってほしい
I want the world you live in to smile.
だから私は生きている
That is why I am alive.
時計の針にも奪えない力
A power that even clock hands cannot steal.
独りになったから物語が
Because I became alone, the story
落とす影 まだ探してる
casts a shadow I am still searching for.
ああ もう一度だけ会いたい
Ah, I just want to meet once more.
何も怖くはない
Nothing frightens me anymore.
命割り理由に出会えた
I found the reason to risk my life,
燃えて消える意味を知った
I learned the meaning of burning away.
その灯火が視界を照らした
That light illuminated my sight,
青く 青く どこまでも
blue, blue, endlessly.
明日が全てを失っても
Even if tomorrow loses everything,
繋げたことだけは歌ってほしい
I want you to sing of what we connected.
だから私は生きている
That is why I am alive.
欠片の全部で いいえ
With all the fragments... No,
泣かないでって祈るのは
praying "Please don't cry"
足跡の下の涙
are the tears beneath our footsteps.
迷いをのけたつま先で
With toes that cast aside hesitation,
進め 進め 魂ごと
advance, advance with your whole soul.
間違いかどうかなんてことよりも
Rather than whether it was a mistake or not,
あなたのいる世界が続いてほしい
I want the world you live in to continue.
ならば私は戦える
Then I can keep fighting.
たとえそのとき側にいないとしても
Even if I am not by your side at that time.
Sarracenia
[Song: Sarracenia]
この地球上全てが俺の遊び場
This entire Earth is my playground.
半端な覚悟で汚すなよ坊や
Don't mess it up with half-hearted resolve, kid.
リアリスト気取りのビビリ屋
A scaredy-cat pretending to be a realist,
話になんねぇ
you're not even worth talking to.
なんでそんなに自信があるんですか？
"Why are you so confident?"
手前で掴んだ結果だ当たり前じゃん
It's the result I grabbed myself, of course I am.
ジャーナリスト気取りの皮肉屋
A cynic pretending to be a journalist,
話す気になんねぇ
I don't feel like talking to you.
毒を喰らえ 栄養を喰らえ
Eat the poison, eat the nutrition.
テメェの味出しで決まる持ち味を活かせ
Make use of your unique qualities brought out by your taste.
One way or another way お前が一体どうしたいかだっちゃ
One way or another way, it's about what you actually want to do.
さぁおかわりはいかがですか？
So, how about seconds?
夢を越えろ
Transcend your dreams,
そこから上を向けよ
look up from there.
リアルに飢えろ
Starve for reality,
上を 上を Yeah
higher, higher, yeah.
ここまで来いよ
Come all the way here!
Come on, turn up! Come on, turn up!
夢は叶えよう
Let me fulfill my dream,
Ey Woah-woah-woah ここまで来よう
Ey woah-woah-woah, come all the way here.
頭ひりつくリスク買ったまんま
Holding onto risks that make my head throb,
安定も安心も手札にはならない
neither stability nor safety will serve as cards in hand.
好きにやるよ てめえも好きにやんな
I'll do as I like, so do whatever you want too.
離すなよ Baby
Don't let go, baby.
もうちょい遊んで頂戴
Play with me a little more,
馬鹿にしてるって？ とんでもねえ 俺バイキング食べ放題
Making fun of you? Not at all, I'm an all-you-can-eat buffet,
ただ毒に当たってもドンマイ お味のほうはいかがですか？
even if you get poisoned, don't mind—how does it taste?
夢は叶えよう そこから上を向けよう
Let's fulfill our dreams, look up from right there.
リアルに上を 上を Yeah
Truly look higher and higher, yeah.
Woah-woah-woah ここまで来よう
Woah-woah-woah, come all the way here.
感まとめて 感まとめて
Gather your feelings, gather your feelings,
感まとめて 感まとめて Yeah
gather your feelings, gather your feelings, yeah.
夢は叶えよう
Let's fulfill our dreams,
Ey Woah-woah-woah ここまで来よう
Ey woah-woah-woah, come all the way here.
果てない 果たない いくらあっても足りない
Endless, unyielding, no matter how much, it's never enough.
腹いっぱい食べたい てめえをやっときさらわない
I want to eat my fill, I won't sweep you away.
あがくの如くこの街を 欲すものは奪い取るのが勝負
Struggling through this city, snatching what I want is the game.
甘く解く解くクロスモーク 超高級なフルコース
Sweetly melting cross-smoke, a super high-class full course.
数字とかは通す ウォッチウォッチ上手
Pushing through numbers and such, skillful at watching.
もっと勝負勝負 But ノンストップな時で勝つ
More match after match, but winning in nonstop time.
トップ・オブ・ザ・トップ
Top of the top.
夢は叶えよう
Let's fulfill our dreams,
そこから上を向けよう
look up from right there.
リアルに上を 上を Ey
Truly look higher and higher, ey.
Woah-woah-woah ここまで来よう
Woah-woah-woah, come all the way here.
感まとめて 感まとめて
Gather your feelings, gather your feelings,
感まとめて 感まとめて Yeah
gather your feelings, gather your feelings, yeah.
夢は叶えよう
Let's fulfill our dreams,
Ey Woah-woah-woah ここまで来よう
Ey woah-woah-woah, come all the way here.
感まとめて 感まとめて 来よう
Gather your feelings, gather your feelings, come on,
感まとめて 感まとめて Yeah
gather your feelings, gather your feelings, yeah.
夢は叶えよう
Let's fulfill our dreams,
Ey Woah-woah-woah ここまで来よう
Ey woah-woah-woah, come all the way here.
あれが正解なんて
Saying that was the right answer,
誰の成れの果て？
whose ultimate ruin is that?
答えも欲しいのも一個でこれだけ
The answer and what I want is just this one thing.
悩んだってしょうがないじゃんね
There's no point in worrying about it, right?
あれは夢だったって思うことにしたって
Even if I decide to believe it was all just a dream,
でも全然思えないんだけど助けてよフォロワー
I can't feel that way at all, help me out, followers!
抗うだけ若さ負け
Just resisting is losing to youth.
Next, next, lucky, lucky, lucky
アーリーオー 割り切れたらさ
Early-oh, if only I could compartmentalize,
オーリーオー 楽なのにとか
Orly-oh, thinking it would be so much easier...
あぁ もうヤダ
Ah, I hate this already.
マジ新世界か
Is this seriously a new world?
あなた以外は あなた以外はいらない ない ない
Other than you, other than you, I don't need anyone else, no, no!
張らないでよバリア あるはずの何か
Don't put up a barrier, there should be something there.
あったならば Happy, jumpin', yeah
If there is, happy, jumpin', yeah!
あなたのその手とあたしのこの手を
Your hand and this hand of mine,
繋いだら もう二度と離さないわ
once connected, I'll never let go again!
あなたのその手があたしのこの手を
Your hand reaching out to grab this hand of mine,
掴んだら 以後お見知りおきを My love
once held, please keep me in mind from now on, my love.
後半戦が来たー！
The second half is here!
エンジン全開！ Let's go! 盛り上がっていくぞ！ Let's go!
Engine full throttle! Let's go! Let's get hyped! Let's go!
フロウグロウの充電足りてる？ 足りてないよな！ 後半戦も盛り上がっていくぞ！
Are your Flow Glow batteries charged? Not enough, right! Let me hear you get hyped for the second half too!
みんなの心もっとメラメラにしちゃうぞ！ 後半戦も せーの！ うー ビー！
I'm gonna make everyone's hearts burn even hotter! Second half too, ready, set, go! Woo B!
みんなに出会えてとっても幸せです！ 画面の向こうの巡民、声出せ！ ボラー！
I'm so happy to meet everyone! Citizens beyond the screen, make some noise! Vora!
新しい姿のフロウグロウで 新しい曲！ 聴いてくれ、『MAKE IT, BREAK IT』
Flow Glow in our new look with a brand-new song! Listen up: 'MAKE IT, BREAK IT'!
You'll see!
Make it, break it, make it, break it, make it, break it
Lock on
目と目が合えば I know キミこそが相棒
When our eyes meet, I know you're the one, my partner.
メロ掴ませる才能 Make it, break it, make it, break it
A talent for grabbing the melody, make it, break it, make it, break it.
パッと見天使でも 中には潜むデーモン
At first glance an angel, but a demon lurks inside.
So ギャップと愛嬌あれば最強 Haterはシカト
So with contrast and charm, we're unstoppable; ignore the haters.
「へー、あっそ！」
"Oh, really?"
一蓮拓生オーガナイズ 退屈に用は無いの
Sharing the same fate in harmony, no time for boredom.
一線画すよボーダーライン 届かない？ しょーがない
Drawing a distinct line; can't reach? Oh well.
ウチらが集えばバリ Baddest 見惚れちゃうでしょ？
When we gather, we're super baddest; you're mesmerized, right?
Dance, dance, showtime!
神イベ 神演出
God-tier event, god-tier stage direction!
置いていかない絶対
I'll never leave you behind!
ついてきて 5 MCs
Follow us, 5 MCs!
本気の Friday Night
A serious Friday Night!
Make it! Break it!
Make a Revolution
私を貫け かぶけ
Push through my way, show your style!
夢に Koi Koi Koi no
Come on, come on to the dream,
Place will never stop
A place that will never stop!
真ん中打ち抜け 駆け抜け
Strike right through the middle, run through!
Can get it right!
You see Make it! Break it!
Make it! Break it!
Bang, bang, bang!
You see Make it! Break it!
Make it! Break it!
ほら どっちにするの？
Hey, which one will you choose?
続々沸く Floor へ
Towards the floor heating up one after another,
理屈より行動
Action over logic!
If you wanna be my mate
よそ見とかナシで
Don't look anywhere else!
Hype に没頭 Follow 没頭
Immersed in the hype, immersed in following,
アゲわかって
Get into the excitement!
Burn に Hot Hot もっと Hot Hot
Burn it hot hot, even more hot hot,
ハイになっちゃって
Getting so high!
置いていかない絶対
I'll never leave you behind!
ついてきて 5 MCs
Follow us, 5 MCs!
本気の Friday Night
A serious Friday Night!
Make it! Break it!
Brand new generation
感じるまま咲かれ 咲かれ
Bloom just as you feel, bloom!
華麗に Koi Koi Koi no
Splendidly, come on, come on,
One time
Tuna will never stop
底抜け抜け出して
Break out completely,
あきらめはナシ
Giving up is not an option!
You see Make it! Break it!
Make it! Break it!
Bang, bang, bang!
You see Make it! Break it!
Make it! Break it!
朝まで Make a noise!
Make a noise until morning!
FG! 行くぞー！
FG! Let's go!
Make a Revolution
私を貫け かぶけ
Push through my way, show your style!
夢に Koi Koi Koi no
Come on, come on to the dream,
Place will never stop
A place that will never stop!
真ん中打ち抜け 駆け抜け
Strike right through the middle, run through!
Can get it right!
You see Make it! Break it!
Make it! Break it!
Bang, bang, bang!
You see Make it! Break it!
Make it! Break it!
ほら どっちにするの？
Hey, which one will you choose?
いよいよ、次が最後の曲です。
Finally, our next song will be the last one.
聴いてください。
Please listen.
stay by my side
ずっと譲れないみんなとのファーストステージ
Our first stage with everyone that I can't ever give up
気取り込め あれはフェイクフェイス
Putting on airs, that's a fake face,
見せて作ってたハリボテ
A showy facade we put on.
期待と不安詰め込んで
Packed with expectations and anxiety,
歩き出したんだ せーので
We started walking forward together, ready, set, go!
強がってた青ざめたヴィラン
Acting tough, like a pale villain,
でもみんなに気づかされたそのままでええやん
But everyone made me realize it's fine to just be yourself.
勝手な当たり前じゃないこの日々
These days aren't just something to take for granted.
V になっても一緒にいたい by BB
Even as VTubers, I want to stay together, by BB!
気づいたら騒がしい毎日
Before I knew it, every day became so noisy,
違う歩幅 どこに行く私たち
With different strides, where are we heading?
迷う自分 みんなくれる刺激
When I lose my way, everyone gives me inspiration.
馴れ合いじゃない これって素敵？
It's not just cozy compromise—isn't this wonderful?
まだリーダーって胸張れなくとも
Even if I can't proudly call myself a leader yet,
持ってる何かある 盾となる覚悟
There's something I have: the resolve to be your shield.
チームのため私 歌って踊るステージ
For the team, I sing and dance on stage.
FLOW GLOW 刻む日々 めぐるページ
FLOW GLOW carving out the days, turning the pages.
Stay by my side 夜中になってもまだ寝れない
Stay by my side, even late at night, I still can't sleep.
Yeah あとどのくらい 辿り着くあの夢の世界
Yeah, how much further until we reach that dream world?
初めて会った日の また輪になって騒いだり
Remembering the day we first met, gathering in a circle and having fun again,
ここまで歩いてきた 見えぬ今でも覚えてる
We've walked all the way here, even unseen, I still remember it now.
Stay by my side 街角でふたり
Stay by my side, the two of us at the street corner,
By my side 考えてるひとり
By my side, thinking all alone.
無駄にはならないから あの涙も
Because those tears won't be in vain either,
今ここ By my side 寄り添ってる隣
Right now, right here by my side, staying close next to me.
ずっと昔はぐれた炎
A flame that strayed long ago,
夜を必死に照らしたこと
Shining desperately through the night.
集まる星 踊ったこと
Gathering stars dancing together,
それは波長 これからも残る音
That's our wavelength, a sound that will remain.
暗闇の中 見えない S.O.S
An unseen S.O.S inside the darkness,
道標はあなたのサイン
The signpost is your signal.
光よ この手を離さないで
Oh light, don't let go of this hand,
空の始まりより煌めいて
Sparkling brighter than the beginning of the sky.
最高なストーリー 同じ夢追い
The ultimate story, chasing the same dream,
愛じゃない We もうひとりじゃない
It's not just love, we are no longer alone!
隅々まで FLOW GLOW の宇宙
Every single corner is FLOW GLOW's universe,
可能性は未知数 配信に夢中
Endless possibilities, hooked on streaming!
いつかみんなで行こう ワイキキ
Someday let's all go to Waikiki!
ラララ セラヴィー HAPPY 楽しみたい日々
La la la C'est la vie, HAPPY days we want to enjoy!
どこか Name に込めたように
Just like the meaning embedded in our name,
私たちはやれる限界を超えて
We can do this, surpassing our limits!
シナジー充填足りてる？
Is the synergy fully charged?
うん、BB！
Yup, BB!
ボルテージ加熱ゴー！
Voltage heating up, go!
リアライズ突破！
Realize breakthrough!
折り返し行くぞー！
Here comes the final turn, let's go!
Stay by my side 夜中になってもまだ寝れない
Stay by my side, even late at night, I still can't sleep.
Yeah あとどのくらい 辿り着くあの夢の世界
Yeah, how much further until we reach that dream world?
初めて会った日の また輪になって騒いだり
Remembering the day we first met, gathering in a circle and having fun again,
ここまで歩いてきた 見えぬ今でも覚えてる
We've walked all the way here, even unseen, I still remember it now.
上がれ BPM
Raise the BPM!
夜も寝れず置き去りにした生活リズム
Unable to sleep at night, leaving our life rhythm behind,
12ヶ月 ともないと振り返る
Looking back together over 12 months.
愚痴ったりしたっていいんじゃない？
Isn't it fine to complain a little sometimes?
生きてく資格等もない
There's no qualification needed to live!
ひとりで抱え込むなよ
Don't bottle it all up by yourself!
腹割って最後に
Opening our hearts up in the end,
自分らしくいよ 心配ない
Be yourself, no need to worry!
美味しいもの食べいこ 次行こう！
Let's go eat something delicious, on to the next!
Stay by my side 夜中になってもまだ寝れない
Stay by my side, even late at night, I still can't sleep.
Yeah あとどのくらい 辿り着くあの夢の世界
Yeah, how much further until we reach that dream world?
初めて会った日の また輪になって騒いだり
Remembering the day we first met, gathering in a circle and having fun again,
ここまで歩いてきた 見えぬ今でも覚えてる
We've walked all the way here, even unseen, I still remember it now.
街角で2人
Two of us on the street corner
stay by my side 街角で2人
stay by my side, two of us on the street corner
by my side 考えてる1人
by my side, one thinking alone
無駄にはならないから あの涙も
Because even those tears won't be in vain
いまここ by my side 寄り添ってる隣
Right here now, by my side, right next to me
はい！ということで後半ノンストップで駆け抜けてきましたが、ご覧の通り衣装チェンジしてます！
Alright! So we ran through the second half non-stop, but as you can see, we changed our outfits!
イエーイ！
Yay!
いや本当に1人1人個性がめちゃくちゃ主張されていて素敵！
Honestly, everyone's personality really shines through, it's so wonderful!
ニコたんはかっこいいし！
Nico-tan is so cool!
りっちゃんはカッコ可愛いし！
Ritchan is cool and cute!
すっちゃんはもう可愛すぎるし！
Succhan is just way too cute!
可愛いね！
So cute!
それになんと言っても、ビビたん！
And above all, Vivi-tan!
え？
Huh?
可愛いね！
You're cute!
何その言い方ー！
What's with that tone?!
すっちゃんも可愛いニコな！みんなに言ってる！
Succhan is cute too, Nico! You're saying that to everyone!
なんと！ここで嬉しいお知らせがあります！
Guess what! We have some exciting news for you here!
何ー？
What is it?
このFLOW GLOWの3Dお披露目ライブ、なんとXのトレンドで1位をとれましたー！
This FLOW GLOW 3D debut live stream actually hit #1 on X trends!
やったー！
Yay!
ちょっと嬉しくてね！感謝で！
We're just so happy and grateful!
さあ、それではここまでを振り返っていきたいと思います！
Now then, let's take a look back at what we've done so far!
まず、わたくし莉々華がダリアと『UP-BUUN-BUUN』のメドレーを披露させていただきました！
First, I, Riona, performed a medley of 'Dahlia' and 'UP-BUUN-BUUN'!
『披露させていただきました』じゃないですよ！もっとオブラートに包んで！エロが出てるよ！
Don't say 'performed' like it's no big deal! Wrap it in a softer phrase! Your sexiness was showing!
ジャズダンスとバレエのガールズを披露させていただきました！セクシーだったかな？
I performed a jazz and ballet girls-style dance! Was I sexy?
続いては？
Next up?
はい！千早がトロンボーンとギターを自分で弾きまして、ギターの弾き語りで『欲望に満ちた青年団』を歌わせていただきました！
Yes! I, Chihaya, played the trombone and guitar myself, singing 'Yokubou ni Michita Seinendan' acoustic style!
みんなに披露できて嬉しいです！
I'm so glad I could show everyone!
そして？
And next?
はい！そしてビビはですね、メイクを生かした『鏡』という楽曲を歌わせていただきました！
Yes! And I, Vivi, sang a song called 'Kagami' utilizing my makeup look!
メイクの変化、見てくれたかな？
Did you notice my makeup change?
お尻見たの？本当！
Did you look at my butt?! Really?
やめてー！はい、そして続いては？
Stop it~! Alright, and next up?
はい！ニコたんは大好きなBUMP OF CHICKENさんの『青の朔日』を、実はギターパパです！実パパです！
Yes! I sang BUMP OF CHICKEN's 'Ao no Tsuitachi', which I love, with my real dad on guitar! My actual dad!
リアルパパと演奏しました！
I performed with my real dad!
ニコたんのいろんな思いを込めて歌わせていただいたので、またアーカイブとか見てもらえたら嬉しいです！
I sang it with all of my feelings, so I'd be really happy if you check out the archive!
そしてお次は？
And next?
はい！響はさらさにゃんとギャルのメドレーを踊らせていただきました！
Yes! I danced to a medley of Sarasa-nyan and Gal songs!
結構ね、かっこよく踊れたんじゃないでしょうか！
I think I was able to dance pretty coolly!
3メートルだわ！今は3メートルあるわ！
You were like 3 meters tall! You felt 3 meters tall!
みんなのソロを楽しんでもらった後は、私たちの新曲、そしてライブのタイトルにもなっております『MAKE IT, BREAK IT』を初披露させていただきました！
After everyone enjoyed the solo performances, we debuted our new song, which is also the title of this live show, 'MAKE IT, BREAK IT'!
やったー！
Yay!
そのあとは、私たちがこの間出させていただいたシングル『stay by my side』を披露させていただきました！
After that, we performed our previously released single 'stay by my side'!
そして！ここで配信を見てくれているみんなにお知らせがあります！
And! Right now, we have an announcement for everyone watching the stream!
なんだなんだー？
What is it, what is it?
お知らせは私たちと同じ5つあるので、1人1人紹介させていただきたいと思います！
We have 5 announcements, just like the 5 of us, so we'd like to introduce them one by one!
トップバッターはビビ！よろしく！
First up is Vivi! Take it away!
ハイハイ！それじゃあこちらをご覧ください！どうぞ！
Alright! Well then, please take a look at this! Here you go!
ファーストアルバム『FLOW GLOW』についてです！発売日は来年1月21日！デビュー曲『FG ROADSTER』のほか、気鋭のサウンドクリエイター陣が手掛ける全9曲を収録しています！
It's about our 1st album 'FLOW GLOW'! The release date is next year on January 21st! It includes 9 songs in total, including our debut song 'FG ROADSTER' and tracks by talented sound creators!
すごーい！
Amazing!
通常盤はAタイプ、Bタイプあり、公式EC版と全国流通版では特典内容も違います！まあ皆さん、この際どちらもゲットしちゃってください！
The standard edition comes in Type-A and Type-B, with different bonus items for the official EC version and nation-wide retail version! Well everyone, feel free to get both!
そして！冒頭にも言った重大発表がこちら！
And! Here is the major announcement we mentioned at the start!
アルバムのリード曲になっている『MAKE IT, BREAK IT』について続報があります！先ほど披露した6thシングル『MAKE IT, BREAK IT』のデジタルリリースが決定しました！
We have further news regarding 'MAKE IT, BREAK IT', the album's lead track! The digital release for our 6th single 'MAKE IT, BREAK IT' that we just performed has been confirmed!
やったー！
Yay!
デジタルリリースは明日、11月24日です！みんな絶対チェックしてやー！
The digital release is tomorrow, November 24th! Everyone, make sure to check it out!
そしてこの『MAKE IT, BREAK IT』のMVの公開なんですが...
And regarding the release of the music video for 'MAKE IT, BREAK IT'...
普段言ったら楽曲のリリースとほぼ同時に公開やねんけど、運営さんがですね、もっともっといいものにしたいということで、公開を延期することになりました！
Normally it would drop almost simultaneously with the track release, but the staff wanted to make it even better, so the MV release has been postponed!
えー！気になるね！まあそちらのMVには、3Dになった...
Ehh?! We're curious! Well, in that MV, our 3D models...
私たちが登場します！
We are making our appearance!
さあ、皆さん！どんな内容に仕上がっているか、今からめっちゃ楽しみにしててな！
Everyone, please look forward to what we have in store!
かっこよく踊ったもんね！
We danced so cool, right?
ダンスとかもね、やったもんね！
We did dances and stuff too!
はい、続いては千速、お願いします！
Okay, next up, Chihaya, please!
はい！それでは、こちらをご覧ください！どうぞ！
Yes! Well then, please take a look at this! Here you go!
ホロカについてです！
It's about Holoca!
一昨日に発売された千速とニコのスタートデッキ、実は今日のライブでお披露目した新衣装のセカンドカードが収録されているんです！
The Chihaya and Nico start decks released the day before yesterday actually include 2nd cards featuring the new outfits revealed in today's live!
みんなにはね、サプライズのつもりで先行してセカンド衣装を入れてもらったんですが、びっくりしましたか？
We put in the 2nd outfits ahead of time as a surprise for everyone, were you surprised?
バレちゃったね！実はね、出てたんだよね！
It got spoiled, right? Actually, they were already out!
これら2つのスタートデッキは取扱のあるカードショップにて販売中です！気になった方はぜひ手に取ってみてください！
These two start decks are now on sale at participating card shops! If you're interested, please check them out!
ホロカに関する情報はまだまだあります！こちらもご覧ください！どうぞ！
There's still more information about Holoca! Please check this out too! Here you go!
来月19日発売の新規ブースターパック「アヤカシヴァーミリオン」、その中に今日りっちゃんがお披露目した新衣装のセカンドが収録されています！
In the new booster pack "Ayakashi Vermilion" releasing on the 19th of next month, the 2nd card with the new outfit Rion-chan revealed today is included!
え、マジ！？なにそれ！？
Wait, really?! What is that?!
え〜、ちょっといいな〜！スタッフさん！ヴィヴィとすーちゃんの速くお願いしますよ〜！
Ehh, I'm so jealous! Staff members! Please release Vivi and Su-chan's quickly too!
お願いします！お願い！
Please! Pretty please!
はい、では続いてはすーちゃん、お願いします！
Okay, next up, Su-chan, please!
はーい！ホロライブ公式ぬいぐるみブランドの「hololive FRIENDS with u」、通称ホロフレ！ついに私たちFLOW GLOWの5人が登場します！
Yees! From the official Hololive plushie brand "hololive FRIENDS with u", aka Holofre, the 5 of us from FLOW GLOW are finally making our appearance!
やったー！ついにだー！
Hooray! Finally!
今年のEXPOで開発中とお知らせしてから、やっと皆さんに届けできるようになりました！
Since announcing development at this year's EXPO, we can finally deliver them to everyone!
注目は髪型や衣装、とにかく再現度がすごい！
Pay attention to the hair and outfits, the level of detail is amazing!
今日の22時より予約開始となりますのでお見逃しなく！
Pre-orders start at 22:00 today, so don't miss out!
続いてのグッズはこちら！
The next piece of merch is this!
今回お披露目した3Dの姿がアクリルスタンドになります！
Our 3D forms revealed today will become acrylic stands!
先輩たちの3Dアクスタを持ってる人なら分かると思うんですが、かなり大きめのサイズとなっております！
If you own our seniors' 3D acrylic stands, you probably know, but these are pretty large in size!
存在感バッチリな私たちの3Dアクスタ、ぜひ手に取ってみてください！
Our 3D acrylic stands have a great presence, so please be sure to get one!
こちらもホロフレと同じく、今日の22時より予約開始となりますので、合わせてチェックしてくれると嬉しいです！
Just like Holofre, pre-orders start at 22:00 today, so we'd be happy if you checked them out together!
続いてはニコ、お願いします！
Next up, Nico, please!
はーい！
Yeees!
まず、こちらをご覧ください！どうぞ！
First, please take a look at this! Here you go!
タワーレコード渋谷、サンシャインシティアルパ店ほか、全国のタワーレコード12店舗... FLOW GLOWの1stアルバム発売を記念したポップアップの開催が決定！
At Tower Records Shibuya, Sunshine City Alpa store, and 12 Tower Records stores nationwide... A pop-up shop celebrating FLOW GLOW's 1st album release has been confirmed!
今まで公式オンラインでしか手に入らなかったMIX TAPE 1&2のほか、先ほど紹介したFGのホロフレ、グッズも盛りだくさんとなっております！
In addition to MIX TAPE 1 & 2 which were previously only available online, as well as FG's Holofre introduced earlier, there's a ton of merch!
またですね、期間中にグッズをお買い上げの方にはノベルティももらえる予定となっておりますので！
Also, those who purchase merch during this period will receive novelty items!
期間、1月20日から2月8日まで！
The period is from January 20th to February 8th!
グッズに関する詳しい情報やノベルティ条件などについては、12月中旬開設予定の特設ページをご覧ください！
For detailed merch info and novelty conditions, please check the special page scheduled to launch mid-December!
最後はリオナ、お願いします！
Lastly, Riona, please!
はーい！それではこちらをご覧ください、どうぞ！
Yeees! Well then, please take a look at this, here you go!
この後、FLOW GLOW公式チャンネルのメンバーシップにてアフタートークライブがあります！
Right after this, we'll have an after-talk live stream on the official FLOW GLOW channel membership!
そっちにも足を運びたいなというそこのあなた！ぜひ今のうちにメンバーシップの登録をお願いします！
For those of you who want to check that out as well, please join the membership while you can!
そのアフタートークライブはここではなく、別のステージからお届けします！
That after-talk live won't be from here, but delivered from a different stage!
そこでしか聞けないライブの裏話とか、あとは1stアルバムに収録されている曲の中からあの曲を披露したいと思います！
We'll share behind-the-scenes stories you can only hear there, plus perform that song from our 1st album!
どう？ますます気になってきたんじゃない？
How about it? Aren't you getting more and more curious?
気になる！気になる！
Curious! Very curious!
待ってるからね！
We'll be waiting for you!
また、私達一人一人のチャンネルのメンバーシップでは推しカメラ配信もあります！ぜひそっちも覗きに来てね！
Also, on each of our individual channel memberships, there are fan-cam streams! Please come check those out too!
見てねー！
Watch it, okay?!
そして！12月9日からの定期配信は3Dとなります！
And! Starting December 9th, our regular streams will be in 3D!
こちらもお楽しみに！
Look forward to that too!
さて皆様！
Well then, everyone!
楽しい時間はあっという間ですが...
Fun times pass in a flash...
そろそろライブも終了となります！
It's almost time for this live to end!
えー！まだ来たばっかり！
Eh?! We just got here!
いや、誰かつっこまないと...
Hey, someone needs to call them out...
ステージの終わりをね、写真に残したいんですけど...
I wanted to capture the end of the stage in a photo...
自撮り棒持ってきた！
I brought a selfie stick!
じゃあ行くよ！ハイ、チーズ！パシャパシャパシャ...
Alright, here we go! Say cheese! *click click click*
取れた？みんな取れたかな？
Did you take it? Did everyone get it?
よーし、ありがとう！
Alright, thank you!
すーちゃん、やってくれたね！
Su-chan, nicely done!
すーちゃんのおかげでね、素敵な思い出も撮れたところで、ここでメンバー一人一人からファンの皆さんにメッセージをお届けしたいと思います！
Thanks to Su-chan, now that we've captured a wonderful memory, we'd like each member to share a message to the fans!
まずはすーちゃんから！
First up, Su-chan!
はい！FLOW GLOW、そしてFLOWMEE、ここまで一緒に走ってきてくれてありがとうございます！みんなのおかげで3Dになれたよ！ここから先もいろんな思い出をみんなと一緒に作っていきたいです！よろしくね！
Yes! FLOW GLOW, and FLOWMEE, thank you for running alongside us all this way! Thanks to everyone, we made it to 3D! Going forward, I want to keep making all kinds of memories with you all! Please treat us well!
はい！
Yeah!
いつも応援してくださるフロウミーのみなさん、そして...
To all the Flowmees who always support us, and...
メンバーみんな、いつもありがとう！
all the members, thank you as always!
みんながいるからここまで来れました！
We were able to make it this far because of you all!
2周年目もみんなと一緒にどんどん花道登っていきましょう！
In our second year, let's keep climbing the path to glory together with everyone!
これからもよろしくね！ほんまにありがとう！
Please keep supporting us! Thank you so much!
さあ、続きましてニコはどうですか？
Now then, moving on, how about you, Niko?
FG... はい、出会ってくれてありがとう。
FG... Yes, thank you for finding us.
ファンのみなさんも... ありがとう。
To all the fans too... thank you.
FLOWGLOWというダイヤモンドに気づけたあなた、天才じゃあ！
You who noticed the diamond that is FLOWGLOW, you're a genius!
これからも愛しよう、フロウミー。ありがと。
Let's keep loving each other, Flowmees. Thank you.
あ、はい！はい！ありがとうございます！
Ah, yes! Yes! Thank you very much!
いや本当にね、今日という日をこの5人で迎えられたことが本当に嬉しく思いますし...
Honestly, being able to reach this day together as five members makes me so happy, and...
このたくさんの方に我々のね、3Dのお披露目を見守っていただけたことも本当に嬉しく思います。最後まで見ていただいてありがとうございます！
I'm truly grateful that so many people watched over our 3D debut. Thank you so much for watching until the end!
ここからね、我々5人がもっともっと未来に向かって突き進んでいく姿、絶対に見逃さないでくださいね！今日は本当にありがとう！
From here on out, please don't miss a single moment as the five of us push forward toward the future! Thank you so much for today!
メン限も待ってます！
We'll be waiting in the member-only streams too!
待ってるよ〜
We'll be waiting!
はい、最後、りっちゃん！
Okay, lastly, Ricchan!
はい！
Yes!
デビュー当初からずっと夢だった歌って踊る姿をお届けできたことを本当に嬉しく思います！
Showing everyone us singing and dancing, which has been my dream since debut, makes me so truly happy!
ここまで応援してくださって本当にありがとうございます！
Thank you all so much for supporting us up to this point!
そしてね、私たちはこれからも...
And you know, from now on, we will also...
ちょっとおいでよ！ちょっとおいでよみんな！
Come over here for a sec! Everyone, come over!
おいおいおい！まだいいところ...
Hey, hey, hey! I was just getting to the good part...
団子みたいになってる！やめてね！
You're clumping together like dango! Stop it!
ああ！りおなが塞がれちゃった！
Ah! Riona got totally blocked out!
私喋ってるじゃん！
Hey, I was speaking!
一言、一言ある？
Any last words? Do you have something to say?
ちょっと男子ー！
Hey, you boys!
あ、まだ... あ、ごめんねごめんね。
Ah, wait... Ah, sorry, sorry.
あのね、これからもね、私たち一人一人の歩みをね、みんなに見守ってほしいんだ！
You know, from now on, I want everyone to keep watching over each of our journeys!
だから、FLOWGLOWのこと、みんなこれからもよろしくね！
So please keep supporting FLOWGLOW in the future as well!
よろしくね〜！
Please do~!
はい、どうぞアンコール！
Alright, go ahead with the encore!
どうぞどうぞ！違うよ！アンコールじゃないのよ！
Go ahead! No, wait! It's not encore time yet!
バレてるバレてる！
They caught on, they totally caught on!
ここじゃないか。ちょっと早かったね。
Guess not here. It was a bit too early.
わかりする？これ終わりなのー？！
Are we leaving? Is this the end?!
じゃあバイバイしようか。最後に挨拶する？
Then let's say bye-bye. Shall we do our final greeting?
そうだね。それじゃあ、私たち...
Right. Well then, we are...
せーの！FLOWGLOWでしたー！
One, two! We were FLOWGLOW!
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you so much!
ん〜〜〜マッ！
Mwah!
フロウミー、大好きやで！チュッ！
Flowmees, I love you all! Mwah!
本当にありがとう。チュッ。
Thank you so much. Mwah.
な、なんだそれ！ありがとう！んー...マッ！
W-What was that?! Thank you! Mwah!
ありがとう。
Thank you.
フロウミー！アンコールありがとう！
Flowmees! Thank you for the encore!
今日は最高のライブでした！
Today was the best live performance!
みんな楽しんでくれたかなー？
Did everyone enjoy it?
やっぱこれ！やっぱりこの曲！FG ROADSTER！
After all, it's this! It's gotta be this song! FG ROADSTER!
搭載V8エンジン
Equipped with a V8 engine
第7感持ってる原人
A primitive human with a 7th sense
6するこの世界と全人類
Sickening this world and all humanity
この5人でゲームをチェンジ
The five of us changing the game
唸る4輪発射せよ
Four roaring wheels, launch away!
皆さん3キュウサランヘヨ
Thank you everyone, saranghaeyo
操る2台のturntable
Controlling two turntables
獲る1番ここground 0
Claiming #1 right here at Ground 0
リスク超えて挑戦
Taking on the challenge beyond all risk
千 百 十 SETS THE TOWN TEN!
1000, 100, 10, sets the town, 10!
千 登りあげる CHART TEN!
1000, climbing up the chart, 10!
座布団敷く SHOW TEN!
Laying down cushions for Shoten!
舞い込め FG ROADSTER
Fly in, FG ROADSTER!
特殊部隊集合 能力者
Special forces assemble, ability users!
この歴史に名を彫る 彫刻家
Sculptors carving our names into history!
ちぎれて置き去り革の靴
Leather shoes torn off and left behind!
超高速でぶち抜いていく大気圏
Piercing through the atmosphere at ultra-high speed!
エンジンからジェットの滑走 揺れている海域へ
Jetting off from the engine into the swaying seas!
眼下に広がる対照 超えてく階級制
The contrast spreading below, transcending classes!
バックミラーにビッグブルーが映ってる IVY
Big Blue reflected in the rearview mirror, IVY!
FIRE! 打ち上げ世代から飛んでいくウチラ世代
FIRE! From launch generation to our generation!
この燃料 尽きてない
This fuel hasn't run out!
ガス欠前すし食べたい！
I wanna eat sushi before running out of gas!
見適えてる世界 Vision
The world we're eyeing, Vision!
燃えてるメンバー 一同
All members fired up together!
只今現在進行形 超えてく世界規模
Right now in real time, going global!
叶うはずの Monster
A monster bound to come true,
心臓が Monster
A heart like a monster!
エイリアン 華麗に Dance
Aliens dancing in style,
FG パリピ波
FG party people wave!
光る鉄の ROSTER
Shining iron roster,
HEAVY BOOSTER
目覚めてく本能
Instincts awakening,
青い炎
A blue flame!
BFF LET'S GO OUT
解けない謎 0から
Unraveling mysteries from zero,
空まで 囚われ
Captivated all the way to the sky!
走る FG ROADSTER
Racing FG ROADSTER,
唸る BOOSTER
Roaring booster!
ROAD ROADSTER
SPACE BEAT
IMAGINARY
ノウハウ築くバカ
Fools building up know-how,
ハンダで裁く助手席も
Soldering even in the passenger seat!
複写の挑戦状 中バカ
Copying challenge letters, mid-tier fools,
次元が違う連中バカ
Fools in a whole different dimension!
コーナー責めてのギリギリ
Pushing the limits on every corner,
モーター全開 ジービービー
Motor at full throttle, revving wild!
ソナーからの未知 ピーピー
Beeping signals of the unknown from sonar,
尾羽が ピチピチ
Tail feathers lively and jumping!
タイヤ焦がしてドーナツターン
Burning rubber with donut turns,
弾け飛んでくドラム缶
Sending oil drums flying!
顧客満足度高くてぶち上がってるお客さん
Customer satisfaction sky-high, audience hyped up!
0から最高到達点
Reaching the highest peak from zero,
タネ出てる太陽光発電
Solar power generating energy,
探査するこの小惑星
Exploring this asteroid!
超覚醒 突入ボーナスステージ
Super awakening, entering the bonus stage!
一直線伸びてる道路
A road stretching out in a straight line,
倍ブレ we are 止まらないカバー
Doubling the vibe, an unstoppable crew!
速度増し上がってる鼓動
Heartbeats racing as speed increases,
臨界重力 脱ぎ捨て上昇
Shedding critical gravity and ascending!
開拓しまくっていくフロンティア
Blazing trails through the frontier,
旅立つ ROADSTER ONLY ONE
The one and only ROADSTER setting off!
アクセル踏み込んでくドンピシャ
Stepping on the gas right on point,
飛んでいく日本遺産
Soaring high, a Japanese heritage!
1億馬力の充電
Charging up 100 million horsepower,
火星のホテルが休憩所
A hotel on Mars is our pit stop!
並んで走行 UFO
Cruising side-by-side with UFOs,
降り立つ SPACE STATION
Landing on the SPACE STATION!
物語の継承
Carrying on the story,
まるで旧約聖書
Just like the Old Testament,
この先何世紀も生息
Thriving for centuries to come,
生き延びて結果出す成功
Surviving and delivering successful results!
叶うはずの Monster
A monster bound to come true,
心臓が Monster
A heart like a monster!
エイリアン 華麗に Dance
Aliens dancing in style,
FG パリピ波
FG party people wave!
光る鉄の ROSTER
Shining iron roster,
HEAVY BOOSTER
目覚めてく本能
Instincts awakening,
青い炎
A blue flame!
BFF LET'S GO OUT
解けない謎 0から
Unraveling mysteries from zero,
空まで 囚われ
Captivated all the way to the sky!
走る FG ROADSTER
Racing FG ROADSTER,
唸る BOOSTER
Roaring booster!
ROAD ROADSTER
SPACE BEAT
IMAGINARY
以上 私たち...
That's all from us...
FLOW GLOW でした！
We were FLOW GLOW!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
それじゃあいくよ
Alright, here we go!